(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-16T22:47:06.532282",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshieyomi" now accepting new members!
「GUM & DROP」好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" is now streaming!
星街すいせい Official Event「PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「Travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE「Project: Allegria」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE "Project: Allegria"
「Once Upon a Stellar」オフィシャルグッズラインナップ
"Once Upon a Stellar" Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshieyomi" now accepting new members!
「GUM & DROP」好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" is now streaming!
星街すいせい Official Event「PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「Travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE「Project: Allegria」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE "Project: Allegria"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRO
2027.2.11 (THU)
Thursday, February 11, 2027
Once Upon a Stellar
OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」
新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP
好評配信中！
Now streaming!
Pajama Party Vol. 2 with Hoshimachi Suisei
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「travelogue」
TRACK LIST
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRO
2027.2.11 (THU)
Thursday, February 11, 2027
Once Upon a Stellar
OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」
新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP
好評配信中！
Now streaming!
Pajama Party Vol. 2 with Hoshimachi Suisei
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
大分：2027.2.7 / 石川：2027.2.20 / 秋田：2027.2.27
Oita: Feb 7, 2027 / Ishikawa: Feb 20, 2027 / Akita: Feb 27, 2027
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP 「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: "travelogue"
TRACK LIST: M01 Hyper Vip / M02 Nonsense / M03 閃光 / M04 404
TRACK LIST: M01 Hyper Vip / M02 Nonsense / M03 Flash / M04 404
2027.2.11 MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA
Feb 11, 2027: Midnight Grand Orchestra
2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar ARENA TOUR 2026
OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub: Hoshiyomi
新規会員受付中！
Now accepting new members!
星街すいせい 「GUM & DROP」
Hoshimachi Suisei: "GUM & DROP"
好評配信中！
Now streaming on major digital platforms!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
大分：2027.2.7 / 石川：2027.2.20 / 秋田：2027.2.27
Oita: Feb 7, 2027 / Ishikawa: Feb 20, 2027 / Akita: Feb 27, 2027
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP 「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: "travelogue"
TRACK LIST: M01 Hyper Vip / M02 Nonsense / M03 閃光 / M04 404
TRACK LIST: M01 Hyper Vip / M02 Nonsense / M03 Flash / M04 404
2027.2.11 MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA
Feb 11, 2027: Midnight Grand Orchestra
2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar ARENA TOUR 2026
OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: travelogue
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE「Project: Allegra」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE: Project: Allegra
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: travelogue
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE「Project: Allegra」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE: Project: Allegra
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2ND LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Suisei Hoshimachi Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" is now streaming!
Pajama Party Vol.2 With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
Pajama Party Vol. 2 with Suisei Hoshimachi
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: "travelogue"
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2ND LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Suisei Hoshimachi Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" is now streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「Travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 'Travelogue'
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live: Project ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub 'Hoshiyomi' now accepting new members!
「GUM & DROP」好評配信中！
GUM & DROP is now available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「Travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 'Travelogue'
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live: Project ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub 'Hoshiyomi' now accepting new members!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" Now accepting new members!
「GUM & DROP」好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now available on streaming platforms!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event「Pajama Party Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party Vol.2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live「PROJECT: ALLEGRO」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live "PROJECT: ALLEGRO"
「Once Upon a Stellar」OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
"Once Upon a Stellar" Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" Now accepting new members!
「GUM & DROP」好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now available on streaming platforms!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event「Pajama Party Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party Vol.2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now accepting new members!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[Gum & Drop - Now Available!]
Pajama Party Vol. 2 with HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP 「travelogue」
[Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: travelogue]
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now accepting new members!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[Gum & Drop - Now Available!]
Pajama Party Vol. 2 with HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event - Pajama Party vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event - Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra - 1st EP 「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra - 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra - 2nd Live 「Project: ALLEGRO」
Midnight Grand Orchestra - 2nd Live "Project: ALLEGRO"
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Open for New Members!
ガムにドロップ
Gum and drops,
君のポッケの中に隠した
hidden inside your pocket.
甘くて苦い恋の味は
The sweet and bitter taste of love
いつまでも消えないままで
remains forever, never fading away.
味のしなくなったガムを
Like continuing to chew on a piece of gum
噛み続けているような
that has completely lost its flavor...
退屈な日々も君となら
even boring days, if I'm with you,
カラフルに染まっていく
will be colored in vivid hues.
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event - Pajama Party vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event - Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra - 1st EP 「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra - 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra - 2nd Live 「Project: ALLEGRO」
Midnight Grand Orchestra - 2nd Live "Project: ALLEGRO"
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Open for New Members!
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now accepting new members!
Gum & Drop Hoshimachi Suisei 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" by Hoshimachi Suisei
Now streaming!
Pajama Party Vol. 2 with Hoshimachi Suisei
Official Event "Pajama Party Vol. 2"
with Hoshimachi Suisei
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP「travelogue」TRACK LIST
Midnight Grand Orchestra
1st EP "travelogue" Track List
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA (2nd LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Midnight Grand Orchestra
2nd Live Project: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
"Once Upon a Stellar"
Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now accepting new members!
Gum & Drop Hoshimachi Suisei 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" by Hoshimachi Suisei
Now streaming!
Pajama Party Vol. 2 with Hoshimachi Suisei
Official Event "Pajama Party Vol. 2"
with Hoshimachi Suisei
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP「travelogue」TRACK LIST
Midnight Grand Orchestra
1st EP "travelogue" Track List
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA (2nd LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Midnight Grand Orchestra
2nd Live Project: ALLEGRIA
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA (2nd LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRA (2027.2.11 THU)
Midnight Grand Orchestra (2nd Live) Project: ALLEGRA (Feb 11, 2027 THU)
星街すいせい アリーナツアー 2024 「Once Upon a Stellar」 オフィシャルグッズラインナップ
Hoshimachi Suisei Arena Tour 2024 "Once Upon a Stellar" Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Open for New Members!
星街すいせい 「GUM & DROP」 好評配信中！
Hoshimachi Suisei - "GUM & DROP" Now Available on Streaming Platforms!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event 「Pajama Party Vol.2 with HOSHIMACHI SUISEI」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party Vol.2 with Hoshimachi Suisei"
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP 「travelogue」 Track List
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue" Track List
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA (2nd LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRA (2027.2.11 THU)
Midnight Grand Orchestra (2nd Live) Project: ALLEGRA (Feb 11, 2027 THU)
星街すいせい アリーナツアー 2024 「Once Upon a Stellar」 オフィシャルグッズラインナップ
Hoshimachi Suisei Arena Tour 2024 "Once Upon a Stellar" Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Open for New Members!
星街すいせい 「GUM & DROP」 好評配信中！
Hoshimachi Suisei - "GUM & DROP" Now Available on Streaming Platforms!
星街すいせい Official Event
Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event
Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project "ALLEGRO"
Once Upon a Stellar Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」
新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now Accepting New Members!
Gum & Drop
好評配信中！
Now Available!
星街すいせい Official Event
Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event
Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project "ALLEGRO"
Once Upon a Stellar Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」
新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now Accepting New Members!
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now Available!
星街すいせい Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party Vol. 2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE PROJECT "ALLEGRIA"
Once Upon a Stellar Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now Available!
星街すいせい Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party Vol. 2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE PROJECT "ALLEGRIA"
[2ND LIVE] PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」
新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP
好評配信中！
Now available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event
「Pajama Party Vol. 2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event:
Pajama Party Vol. 2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA
1st EP「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra
1st EP: travelogue
[2ND LIVE] PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」
新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP
好評配信中！
Now available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event
「Pajama Party Vol. 2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event:
Pajama Party Vol. 2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 「Travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: Travelogue
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project 「ALLEGRIA」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRIA
「Once Upon a Stellar」 Arena Tour 2026 Official Goods Lineup
"Once Upon a Stellar" Arena Tour 2026: Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi": Now accepting new members!
Hoshimachi Suisei 「GUM & DROP」 好評配信中！
Hoshimachi Suisei "GUM & DROP": Now Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 「Travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: Travelogue
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project 「ALLEGRIA」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRIA
「Once Upon a Stellar」 Arena Tour 2026 Official Goods Lineup
"Once Upon a Stellar" Arena Tour 2026: Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi": Now accepting new members!
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now Accepting Members!
「GUM & DROP」好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now Available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event「Pajama Party Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event
"Pajama Party Vol. 2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP
"travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE「PROJECT: ALLEGRIA」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE
"PROJECT: ALLEGRIA"
「Once Upon a Stellar」オフィシャルグッズラインナップ
"Once Upon a Stellar" Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi"
Now Accepting Members!
「GUM & DROP」好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now Available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event「Pajama Party Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event
"Pajama Party Vol. 2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP
"travelogue"
Once Upon a Stellar
本日は、「Once Upon a Stellar」にご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to "Once Upon a Stellar" today.
まもなく、開演いたします。
The show will begin shortly.
開演に先立ちまして、お客様に、いくつかご案内とお願いがございます。
Prior to the start of the show, we have a few announcements and requests for the audience.
客席内での...
In the auditorium...
...となっております。おタバコを吸われる方は、所定の喫煙所をご利用ください。
...is prohibited. If you wish to smoke, please use the designated smoking areas.
また、客席内での許可のない撮影、録音、録画などの行為は、固くお断りいたします。
Additionally, unauthorized photography, recording, and filming inside the seating area are strictly prohibited.
万一、このような行為を発見した場合は、機器を没収の上、ご退場いただく場合もございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
In the event that such actions are discovered, the equipment may be confiscated and you may be asked to leave, so please understand this in advance.
お近くで不審物や、不審な行為を見かけられた場合は、お近くの係員までお申し出ください。
If you see any suspicious objects or behavior, please report them to a nearby staff member.
本日の公演は、客席内に撮影用のカメラが入っております。
Today's performance will be recorded by cameras in the seating area.
皆様が映り込む場合がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware that you may be captured on camera.
周辺のお客様の視界を妨げるような、大きな帽子の着用、
Please refrain from wearing large hats
装飾品などの着用は、他のお客様のご迷惑となりますので、お控えいただきますようお願いいたします。
or accessories that may obstruct the view of those around you.
また、公演中の応援グッズ、ペンライト、
Also, the use of cheering goods, penlights,
その他光り物のご使用は、演出の都合上、すべて禁止とさせていただきます。
and other glowing items is strictly prohibited due to stage production.
以上のことが守られない場合、公演を一時中断、もしくは中止させていただく場合や、
Failure to comply with these rules may result in the suspension or cancellation of the show, or
ご退場いただく場合もございます。
you may be asked to leave.
皆様のご理解、ご協力をお願いいたします。
We appreciate your understanding and cooperation.
また、周囲のお客様のご迷惑となるような、
In addition, please refrain from
大声での会話、歓声、および発声等は、お控えいただきますようお願いいたします。
loud conversations or cheering that may disturb others.
公演中、体調を崩された場合、また、
During the performance, if you feel unwell,
周りに体調の悪そうな方がいらっしゃる場合は、お近くの係員までお申し出ください。
or see anyone else who does, please notify the staff.
なお、本日、終演後は、規制退場とさせていただきます。
Furthermore, after the performance, exits will be regulated.
係員の誘導があるまで、ご自分のお席でお待ちいただきますようお願いいたします。
Please remain in your seats until guided by the staff.
皆様のご理解、ご協力をお願いいたします。
We appreciate your understanding and cooperation.
本日は、携帯電話、スマートフォン、タブレット等の電源をお切りいただくか、マナーモードに設定の上、おカバンにおしまいください。
Please turn off your phones and other devices, or set them to silent mode and keep them in your bags.
客席内での撮影、録音は固くお断りいたします。
Photography and audio recording inside the seating area are strictly prohibited.
間もなく開演いたします。今しばらくお待ちください。
The performance will begin shortly. Please wait a little longer.
あ、そこの星、もうちょっと右しゅいな。
Ah, that star over there... a little more to the right, please.
あ、もっと左しゅい？
Ah, more to the left?
あ、そうそうそうそう！
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes!
いい感じしゅいねー！
Looking good!
じゃ、スイッチ、オーン！
Now, switch... on!
みんなー！ヤッホー！
Everyone! Yahoo!
すいちゃんしゅいよー！
It's Sui-chan!
星詠みのみんな、今日が初めてのみんな、
To all the Hoshiyomi, and to everyone here for the first time,
会いに来てくれて、ありがとうしゅい！
thank you so much for coming to see me!
いやー、もうすぐ始まるんだけど、その前に！
Well, it's about to start, but before that!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
ライブマナー！
Live manners!
ということで、すいちゃんからみんなに、
And so, from Sui-chan to everyone...
ライブを楽しむためのお願いごとが３つ、ありしゅい！
...there are three requests to help you enjoy the concert!
まず1つ目！
First of all!
ライブ中は、撮影、録音は、できないしゅいよ！
Recording and photography are not allowed during the live performance!
今日しか見られない景色、一緒に楽しむしゅい！
Let's enjoy this scenery that can only be seen today, together!
次！２つ目！
Next! Number two!
応援してくれるのは、すっごく嬉しいしゅい！
I'm super happy that you're supporting me!
でも、周りが見えなくなると...
But if you lose sight of your surroundings...
すいちゃん可愛いよー！
Sui-chan, you're so cute!
すいちゃん今日も可愛いよー！
Sui-chan, you're cute today too!
すいちゃん！
Sui-chan!
超可愛い！
Super cute!
すいちゃん！
Sui-chan!
すいちゃーーん！
Sui-chaaan!
うおおおお！
Whoaaa!
すいちゃーーん！
Sui-chaaan!
今日も可愛いーー！
You're cute today too!
ということで、
And so,
周りがびっくりしちゃうような大声やコールは、ダメしゅい！
loud shouting or call-outs that startle those around you are a no-no!
あと、「すいちゃんは今日も可愛い！」コールも、
Also, the "Sui-chan is cute today too!" call...
すいちゃんが合図するまで、取っておいてしゅいよ！
...please save it until I give you the cue!
そして、３つ目！
And thirdly!
みんな、ペンライト持ってるしゅいか？
Does everyone have their penlights?
見せて見せて！
Show me, show me!
おおー！
Ooh!
ライブが始まったら、もっと凄くなるしゅいね！
Once the live starts, it's going to look even more amazing!
でも、使うときにはルールがあるしゅい。
But there are rules for using them.
改造ペンライトや、
Modified penlights,
26cmを超えるもの、
ones exceeding 26cm,
眩しすぎるものは、使っちゃダメしゅい。
and overly bright ones are not allowed.
みんなでルールを守って、楽しいライブにするしゅいよ！
Let's all follow the rules to make this a fun live concert!
協力してくれるしゅいか？
Will you cooperate with me?
じゃ、一回みんなでペンライト消すしゅい！
Then, let's all turn off our penlights for a moment!
せーの！
Ready, set...
完璧！ありがとう！
Perfect! Thank you!
よし、これで準備オッケー！
Alright, we're all set!
みんなも、いけるしゅいかー？！
Are you guys ready too?!
それじゃ！
Well then!
始まるしゅい！
It's starting!
昔々、キラキラと光る、不思議なお城に、
Once upon a time, in a magical castle shining brilliantly,
星街すいせいという女の子が住んでいました。
lived a girl named Hoshimachi Suisei.
そこはまるで、おとぎ話の絵本から飛び出してきたような、
It was a wonderful castle, just like one...
素敵なお城です。
...that jumped right out of a fairy tale picture book.
夜になると、すいせいは窓辺で歌を歌います。
When night fell, Suisei would sing songs by the window.
花火が上がり
As the fireworks go up,
みんなが笑顔になる
everyone starts to smile.
キラキラとまばゆい
Sparkling and dazzling,
星空のステージです
it's a stage under the starry sky.
もう 照らすはずのない
Though it was never meant to shine again,
それぞれの進む先 照らす
it lights up each of our paths ahead.
人の夢 満たすこの心
This heart that fills people's dreams,
僕が誰であれ あくあ
no matter who I am, is Aqua!
そこをどけて ゆずれないわ My Stage
Step aside, I won't give up My Stage!
邪魔しないで
Don't get in my way.
メイクアップして ドレスアップして
Putting on makeup, dressing up,
待ってる人がいるの
there are people waiting for me!
ところでそちら
By the way, how are things
どちら様ですか？
over on your end? Who might you be?
もういいですか？
Are we good to go now?
主役って大変だわ
Being the star is hard work!
ホップステップの
Hop, step, and
精神で
with that spirit,
目と目そらさないでね
don't take your eyes off me, okay?
フリルはどんな衣装にも もうウンザリだわ
Frills on every outfit... I'm so sick of them!
アツいハート ミュージック 浴びてスポットライト
With a hot heart and music, bathing in the spotlight!
たとえどんな 逆境も
No matter what adversity comes,
跳ね返して
I'll bounce right back!
1、2、3で
On one, two, three,
フォールインラブ！
fall in love!
称賛、絶賛、ありがとう
Praise and acclaim, thank you so much!
お利口にしましょう
Let's be on our best behavior!
ちょっとメタみ、ソレみ、ありありで
With a bit of meta-talk and self-awareness here and there,
退屈なんですか？
are you feeling bored?
誰の所為
Whose fault is it?
それでも
Even so,
この世界
in this world,
ご機嫌よう
I bid you adieu!
ポップなフラッシュを
Bathing in the
浴びて
pop flashes,
耳を離さないでね
don't close your ears to me, okay?
あくあ色に
Drenched in Aqua-color,
染まるように 飛び込む世界は回る
the world I dive into spins around.
一度きりの愛に気づいて
Notice this once-in-a-lifetime love,
救い合い、きらきらと 舞い踊り輝け
helping each other, dancing and shining sparklingly!
フリルはどんな衣装にも もうウンザリだわ
Frills on every outfit... I'm so sick of them!
アツいハート ミュージック 浴びてスポットライト
With a hot heart and music, bathing in the spotlight!
たとえどんな エンディングが待ち受けていても
No matter what kind of ending is waiting for us,
跳ね返して
I'll bounce right back!
きっと冷めない心 冷めない夢が
Surely, a heart that won't cool, a dream that won't fade,
フィクションなんかじゃない
is anything but fiction!
たとえ誰が 笑っても
Even if someone laughs at me,
跳ね返して
I'll bounce right back!
1、2、3で
On one, two, three,
フォールインラブ！
fall in love!
Fall in love!
あくあ色に
In Aqua-color,
染まれ
dye yourself!
雨に濡れた髪 撫でてあげる
Let me stroke your hair wet from the rain,
あの日に戻りたいの もう戻れないの
we can never return to the same heat as that day.
You and I, go...
二人きりじゃ足りないよ
Just the two of us isn't enough!
Don't you agree? これ以上いないでね
Don't you agree? Don't stay any longer, okay?
C4、D4、E4 とっておきのTreat
C4, D4, E4, with a special Treat,
期待して
look forward to it!
時計の針よりも 早いの、私
Faster than the hands of a clock, that's me,
Want to dance with me?
1、2、3、4 そう、サボタミー
1, 2, 3, 4, yeah, slacking off,
がむしゃら、みたいね
seems like I'm trying so hard.
So I can't be 足りないよ
So I can't be, it's not enough!
Don't you agree? これ以上いないでね、ええ
Don't you agree? Don't stay any longer, okay? Yeah!
あうと、よ、ごきげんよう
You're out! So, bid you adieu!
揺れるカミ、カミ、ヤミ、ヤミ、ヤミ
Swaying hair-hair, dark-dark-dark,
Sugar and...
Wii-wii-woo かみかみ 暗闇闇
Wii-wii-woo, bite, bite, in the deep darkness...
Wii-wii-woo かみかみ Give me, give me your time
Wii-wii-woo, bite, bite, give me, give me your time!
Wii-wii-woo かみかみ 暗闇闇
Wii-wii-woo, bite, bite, in the deep darkness...
Give me, give me your...
重なった私のロード
My overlapping path...
そう ここからのランウェイ
...yes, is a runway starting from here!
What a life! Give me one!
自由のままでスパイス
Letting my freedom be the spice
What you need? Oh mind!
抜け出せないアディクション
An inescapable addiction
Feel so beautiful!
とっておきのトリートメントさせてね
Let me treat you to something special
私の響かせたい
I want to make it resonate...
胸のヒート 沸き立っているみたい
the heat in my chest... it feels like it's boiling up!
騒ぐ神が 無情に満ちている
The noisy gods are filled with ruthlessness
ちょっとの火傷じゃ足りないよ
A little burn is not enough!
モッシュピット これ以上ないね
This is the ultimate mosh pit!
エイエイオーとよく言った
"Ei-Ei-Oh," they shouted well!
Every moment we touch, let you hot-hot-hot
湧き上がるエモーション
A welling emotion...
騒ぐ神が 無情に満ちている
The noisy gods are filled with ruthlessness
シュガー・オン・イット・タイム
Sugar on it time!
Wii-wii-woo かみかみ 暗闇闇
Wii-wii-woo, bite, bite, in the deep darkness...
Wii-wii-woo かみかみ Give me, give me your time
Wii-wii-woo, bite, bite, give me, give me your time!
Wii-wii-woo かみかみ 暗闇闇
Wii-wii-woo, bite, bite, in the deep darkness...
シュガー・オン・イット・タイム
Sugar on it time!
Wii-wii-woo かみかみ 暗闇闇
Wii-wii-woo, bite, bite, in the deep darkness...
Wii-wii-woo かみかみ Give me, give me your time
Wii-wii-woo, bite, bite, give me, give me your time!
騒ぐ神が
The noisy gods...
無情に満ちている
...are filled with ruthlessness!
ちょっとの火傷じゃ足りないよ
A little burn is not enough!
モッシュピット これ以上ないね
This is the ultimate mosh pit!
エイエイオーとよく言った
"Ei-Ei-Oh," they shouted well!
いたずらな感情が
Mischievous emotions...
歪んで溢れていた
...distorted and overflowed.
勝ち目のないこの衝動が
This hopeless urge...
弱気な気持ちバイバイ
...says goodbye to weak feelings.
あなたの目に映る可愛い私
The cute me reflected in your eyes...
この瞬間を理由に
...using this moment as an excuse...
覗いてみたい 壊れるまで
...I want to peer in until we break.
ロマンスは殺した
I've killed the romance.
Darling, love 聞かせて
Darling, let me hear your love.
今だけは甘え甘えて 夜に甘えて
Just for now, pamper me, spoil me, rely on the night.
ブルーな口づけに意味なんてないの
There's no meaning to a melancholy kiss.
抑えられないよ10秒
I can't hold back for even ten seconds.
私の想う愛情が
The love I envision...
滲んで歪んで溢れていた
...blurred, distorted, and overflowed.
嘘と嘘重ねたゆんだ 正常な思考バイバイ
Piling lies on lies to ease up, bye-bye to normal thoughts.
大きくなったって愛なんて知らないわ
Even when I grow up, I won't know anything about love.
この瞬間をごまかすみたい
It seems like I'm deceiving this moment...
怒ったのは
...the one who got angry...
ロマンスの果て
...was at the end of romance.
よく動く嘘の世界は
This highly active world of lies...
妙にきらめいていて
...sparkles strangely.
どんな毒を飲ませたら
What kind of poison should I feed you...
ねえ このまま連れ出してくれる？
...hey, to make you take me away like this?
さらってみせて
Sweeping me off my feet, show me...
この先も迷って迷って狂うのを見て
...watch me get lost, wander, and go crazy from here on.
だめ このままじゃ 行かないで
No, not like this... don't go!
Darling, love 聞かせて
Darling, let me hear your love.
今だけは揺らいで甘えて 夜に踊って
Just for now, waver, pamper me, and dance into the night.
ループ繰り返す意味なんてないの
There's no meaning to this endless loop.
抑えられないよ10秒
I can't hold back for even ten seconds.
甘い表情で
With a sweet expression...
泥に満ちた歩みは
Our steps covered in mud...
月なき足元
...under feet without a moon.
装うの、デビュタント
Dress up, debutante.
夢を描いたベールで
With a veil painted in dreams...
恥じらったのなら
...if we felt shy,
孤独も溶けてゆくわ
even loneliness would melt away.
偶然だって泣いたってわかってるって
Whether it's coincidence or if I cry, I understand...
ちっぽけなレディー
...that I'm just a tiny lady.
また同じところで
Once again, at the same place,
目を合わす時に
when our eyes meet.
なすがままに
Just let things be,
風に任せて
leave it to the wind.
満ち去るのを待つだけね
Just waiting for it to wax and wane,
そういうの待ってました
I've been waiting for something like that.
大して変わらないフィニッシュ
A finish that doesn't change much,
謎に包まれて
wrapped in mystery.
構いはしない 絡み合っている
I don't care, we are intertwined...
アンダーグッドテイル
...under a good tale.
縛り羽ほどいたふりして
Pretending to have untied my bound wings,
安らぎを手に入れるのなら
if I can obtain peace...
手首ちぎれるまで待った
...I waited until my wrists tore apart.
筋書き通りだな
It's just as planned.
余計になすまままだっても
Even if I go with the flow excessively,
好きなように思ってくれてもいい
you can think of me however you like.
なんてね
Just kidding.
泣いたって歌ってるって
Even if I cry, I'm singing,
もう十分だ
and that's already enough.
なんて焦りだして
Getting impatient,
はまらないだって
saying I don't fit in.
脱ぎ去るさま
The way I shed it all,
風に任せて
leave it to the wind.
悪くないじゃない 確かめて
Isn't it not bad? Verify it.
そういうの待ってました
I've been waiting for something like that.
大して変わらないフィニッシュ
A finish that doesn't change much,
謎に包まれて
wrapped in mystery.
構いはしない 絡み合っている
I don't care, we are intertwined...
アンダーグッドテイル
...under a good tale.
はじける心メロディ
A bursting heart's melody,
次の息を待ってる間の冷たさ
the coldness while waiting for the next breath.
嘘みたいな夜にしたかった
I wanted to make it a night like a lie,
いつも通りから
from the usual...
紡ぐから
...I will spin it.
なすがままに
Just let things be,
風に任せて
leave it to the wind.
満ち去るのを待つだけね
Just waiting for it to wax and wane,
そういうの待ってました
I've been waiting for something like that.
大して変わらないフィニッシュ
A finish that doesn't change much,
謎に包まれて
wrapped in mystery.
構いはしない 絡み合っている
I don't care, we are intertwined...
アンダーグッドテイル
...under a good tale.
まだ絡み合っている
Still intertwined...
アンダーグッドテイル
...under a good tale,
under a good tale,
アンダーグッドテイル
under a good tale.
はい！
Yes!
星街すいせい アリーナツアー 2026
Hoshimachi Suisei Arena Tour 2026...
「Once upon a Stella」へ ようこそー！
...\"Once upon a Stella\", welcome!
この城すごくなーい？
Isn't this castle amazing?
すごい、そうだよねー！
It's amazing, right?
え、あの、1日目も来ました！って人
Um, who here also came on Day 1?
おー、いやいや、多すぎ多すぎ！
Whoa! No, no, way too many!
え、2日目から来ました、今日から来ました！って人
Um, who here came for Day 2—came from today?
おー、めっちゃいる！
Whoa, there are a ton!
え、じゃあ、2日目から来た人は、びっくりしたよね！
Well, those who came from Day 2 must have been surprised, right?
びっくり！そうですよね。
Surprised! Yeah, I bet.
そう、あの、物販で販売してました
Yeah, we were selling it at the merch booth—
絵本「Once upon a Stella、時をかける彗星のお城」の世界観、
the picture book \"Once upon a Stella: The Time-Traveling Comet's Castle\"...
物語を舞台に、こういうお城を建てさせていただきまして
We built this castle based on its story and world,
えー、Stellaチーム...
and the Stella team...
ライブ制作チームの皆さんと一緒にね、この美術、演出、こだわって作らせていただきました！
Along with the live production team, we put a lot of care into creating this set and performance!
拍手！
Applause!
あの、ま、Day 1に来てた人もいっぱいいるということで、
Well, since there are many people here who also came on Day 1...
あの、Day 1では、このお城のすごいところ、
On Day 1, I talked about the amazing part of this castle,
この上の、丸い...
the round thing up there...
アストロラーベと呼ばれる、何だっけ、星図表みたいな、星図盤みたいな、
Called the astrolabe, what was it, like a star chart or star map?
やつがすごいよって話をしたんですけど、え、覚えてますか？Day 1来た人。
I talked about how amazing it is. Do you remember, those who came on Day 1?
Day 2の人も覚えているよって、今言ったよね、絶対に。
Those on Day 2 also said they remember it, didn't you? Absolutely.
え、じゃあちょっと、そうだね、ちょっと違うこと言うならば、あの...
Well then, let's see, if I were to say something a bit different...
バンドさんがお城の上に立ってる！
The band members are standing on top of the castle!
すごくね？
Isn't that amazing?
すごい！
Amazing!
そうだよね。
Right?
はい、あの、いつものバンドメンバーでお送りしております。
Yes, we're bringing this to you with our usual band members.
皆さんよろしくお願いしますね。
Everyone, please treat them well!
はい。えー、スタジオ・ステラ設立して初めてのソロライブということで、
Yes. Well, as this is the first solo live concert since establishing Studio Stella,
私も、こだわり、こだわり抜いてね、もう、毎日のように、あの、スタッフさんと、
I've been extremely particular, almost every day, with the staff members,
「すいちゃん、これ監修してください」「すいちゃん、これも監修、これすいちゃん監修」
they were like, "Sui-chan, please supervise this," "Sui-chan, supervise this too, this is supervised by Sui-chan,"
「えっと、えっと、これは、もっとこう、これはもっとこう、うん、これオッケー、これは連動ですね」って、本当に、
and I was like, "Let's see, this should be more like this, this should be like that, yeah, this is okay, this is coordinated." Truly,
めっちゃ頑張って作ったんで、
we worked really hard to make this,
ぜひ、最後まで、このライブを楽しんで、楽しみ尽くしてください！
so please enjoy this live concert to the absolute fullest until the very end!
昨日と、違うことがあります。
There is something different from yesterday.
それは、
That is...
配信を見てるみんな！
Everyone watching the livestream!
実は、あの、ここら辺に、コメントの雨が、コメント、いえーい！
Actually, right around here, there's a rain of comments... Comments saying, "Yay!"
いえー、うおー、見てるよ、はい、ふー、見てるよ、すいちゃん、っていうね、声が、はい、あります。
"Yay, whoa, I'm watching!", "Yes!", "Woo!", "I'm watching, Sui-chan!" Those kinds of voices are right there.
楽しめているようです。
It seems they're enjoying it.
YouTubeはね、あの、途中までしか見れませんので、
The YouTube stream will only go up to a certain point,
ライブを最後まで見たい方は、
so for those who want to watch the live concert until the end,
概要欄のSPWN、Z-aN、Huluで配信チケットをゲットしてください。
please get your livestream tickets from SPWN, Z-aN, or Hulu linked in the description.
え、なんとね、でもね、いつもだったらここで「なんとごめんなさい、ここでチラ見せは終了」って言うじゃないですか。
And you know, normally I would say, "I'm sorry, but the sneak peek ends here."
なんと今日はここで終わらない！
Surprisingly, today we're not ending here!
すごいでしょ？じゃあ、どこで終わるのか。
Amazing, right? Then where will it end?
ちょっとDay 1来た人はね、「ここじゃね？」ってちょっと予想しながらね、見てください。
For those who came on Day 1, please watch while guessing, "Is it here?"
ということで、ちょっと、お忘れじゃないですか？
So, with that said, haven't you forgotten?
恒例の、あれ、やっちゃいますよ。
Let's do that customary thing.
アリーナの皆さん、いけますか？
Everyone in the Arena, are you ready?
レベル3の皆さん、いけますか？
Everyone on Level 3, are you ready?
レベル5の皆さん、いけますか？
Everyone on Level 5, are you ready?
レベル7の人、いけるんですか？
Those on Level 7, are you ready?
いいね、見えてるからね！遠いなとか思ってんでしょ？レベル7も、
Nice, I can see you! You're thinking, "We're so far away," right? Level 7,
レベル5も、レベル3もね、アリーナの後ろも見えてますからね！
Level 5, Level 3, and the back of the Arena, I can see all of you!
気ぃ抜いちゃダメですよ！
Don't let your guard down!
あ、配信のみんなも、いける？！
Oh, everyone on the livestream, are you ready?!
ありがとうございます。配信のみんなの分も。
Thank you. Thank you to everyone on the livestream too.
それでは、彗星の如く現れたスターの原石！バーチャルアイドルの星街すいせいです！
And so, a star in the rough who swept in like a comet! I am virtual idol Hoshimachi Suisei!
すいちゃんはー？！
Sui-chan is?!
まだいけるな。え？
You guys can still go louder. Huh?
ちょっと今日みんな雨降ったから、しおれちゃってんじゃないの？ねえ。
Since it rained today, are you all a bit withered? Huh?
吹き飛ばそう、ね？この湿気、吹き飛ばそう。もう一回行くよ。
Let's blow it away, okay? Let's blow away this humidity. Let's do it again.
すいちゃんはー？！
Sui-chan is?!
いけるやないの！
Look at that, you can do it!
この後も最後まで、喉枯らしていってくださいね！
Keep shouting and wearing out your throats until the very end!
ワンス・アポン・ア・ステラの物語は、まだまだ始まったばかりです。
Once Upon a Stella's story has only just begun.
みんな、最後までついてきてください。
Everyone, please follow me until the very end.
それでは、次の曲にいきたいと思います。
And now, I'd like to move on to the next song.
聴いてください。
Please listen.
明かりがひとつ灯った と思った
I thought a single light turned on.
天を彩った 秒画 綺麗だ
The painting that colored the sky was beautiful.
僕の吐いた白い息を夜に 消してしまえたらな
If only I could erase the white breath I exhaled into the night.
押し殺して深く沈んだ
Suppressed and deeply sunken,
泣き声さえ聞こえているから
even the sound of crying can be heard.
君を指した不安の靴音を 僕の絵の具で 塗りつぶして
Painting over the footsteps of anxiety pointing at you with my paint...
全部、みどりになって
...all of it, turning into green,
星の海を流れていった
it flowed through the sea of stars.
果てしない闇の中に そっと這わせた 確かな ほら
See, I gently let a certain hope crawl into the endless darkness.
彗星が夜をまたいで飛んだ
The comet crossed the night and flew.
誰もいない夜の空を染めた
It dyed the empty night sky.
深く沈みきった街の中へ 降り注ぐのは 誰の悲しみだろう
What falls into the deeply sunken city? Whose sadness could it be?
星はまた強がって飛んだ
The stars flew, pretending to be strong once again.
靄のかかった思考を回して
Spinning my hazy thoughts,
「いつか出会える」なんて言えなかった
I couldn't say "we'll meet again someday"...
確かな不安を 隠す言葉はまだ
...with the words that hide my certain anxiety, yet.
黒く澄んだ無限の空も
Even the endless sky that cleared into black,
箒星が彩るように
as if a comet colors it...
君を指した不安の靴音を 僕の絵の具で 塗りつぶして
Painting over the footsteps of anxiety pointing at you with my paint...
君の涙をそっと
Gently, your tears...
星の海に流し込んだ
...I poured into the sea of stars.
溢れ出したその光が 誰かをまた救うから
Because that overflowing light will save someone once again.
彗星が僕らの上を飛んだ
The comet flew above us.
この空を突き君に届ける
Piercing this sky to reach you.
言い忘れた言葉の重み聞いて 降り注ぐのは 誰の悲しみだろう
Listen to the weight of the words I forgot to say; what falls, whose sadness could it be?
星はまた強がって飛んだ
The stars flew, pretending to be strong once again.
街の視線を奪い去るように
As if to steal the gaze of the city,
「君とまた出会えるから僕はここで」
"Since I can meet you again, I'll be here..."
星の名前をひとつ 受け止めよう
...to accept one of the stars' names.
悲しみが溢れそうになること 遠くで離ればなれでも
Even when sadness is about to overflow, and even if we are far apart...
僕らは繋がってるから
...we are still connected.
彗星が夜をまたいで飛んだ
The comet crossed the night and flew.
誰もいない夜の空を染めた
It dyed the empty night sky.
深く沈みきった街の中へ 降り注ぐのは 誰の悲しみだろう
What falls into the deeply sunken city? Whose sadness could it be?
星はまた強がって飛んだ
The stars flew, pretending to be strong once again.
靄のかかった思考を回して
Spinning my hazy thoughts,
「いつか出会える」なんて言えなかった
I couldn't say "we'll meet again someday"...
確かな不安を隠す言葉はもう
...with the words that hide my certain anxiety, anymore.
ずっと君の行く先を 探してた
I've been searching for your destination all this time.
トワイライト・ファンタジー
Twilight fantasy
そう 自由 自由 自由 自由 思いのままに 孤独と踊る つかまる衝動
That's right, freedom, freedom, freedom, freedom / Dancing with loneliness as I please, a capturing impulse
もう どうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore
言葉は残しておきたいだけ
I just want to leave my words behind
君の笑顔が本当の気持ち
Your smile is your true feelings
苦し紛れの言い訳は
A desperate excuse...
いらない いらない 君はどう？
...is not needed, not needed. How about you?
希望を失ったみたいな
As if having lost all hope,
心の影を辿り手
following the shadow of the heart.
同じ言葉ばかり繰り返して
Constantly repeating the same words,
それからの向こうで踊る
dancing on the other side of that.
深く深く取り繕うまで 足掻いて泣いて叫んで消えないように
Struggling, crying, screaming, so it won't disappear as we cover up deeply.
魔法みたいな強いもの 主人公なら証明して
If you are the protagonist of something strong like magic, prove it.
最後はどうなってもハッピーエンド するなら好きにさせてよ
No matter how it ends, let me do as I like if it's a happy ending.
もうどうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
まさか負荷に落ちていた無重力
Unbelievably, the zero gravity fallen into gravity,
ミッドナイト飛行
a midnight flight.
秘密の中で交わって飛ぼう
Let's meet and fly in the secret.
kissで最後まで持って行って マスコットたちの足音が
Keep it up with a kiss until the end, the mascot's footsteps...
交じり合う星に追い果て
chasing to the end of the intersecting stars.
正義が嫌いだなんてこの世はすべて終わった相棒さ
Saying you hate justice, this world is completely finished, partner.
もうどうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
曖昧な想いが揺れてる 君の瞳の奥へと
An ambiguous feeling is swaying, deep into your eyes,
ピント合わしてフォーカス
focus, aligning the lens.
ピント外れの真実のそばに居れたらそれだけで
Beside the out-of-focus truth, if I could just be there, with only that,
黒と白の街が滲むんだ 簡単じゃないから もっと
the black and white city bleeds, because it's not simple, more!
クローバー 頭空け立つように 1、2の3で
Clover, as if clearing my head, on the count of one, two, three,
魔法みたいな強いもの そんなもの無くたって...
something strong like magic, even without such a thing,
諦めたってのはもうバッドエンド 最後の勇気を
giving up is already a bad end, the final courage...
もうどうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
火花みたいに燃えた証
The proof that burned like sparks,
いつの日か忘れちゃった
I forgot it someday.
叶わないなんて感情を絞り挟んで特別になるんだろう
Squeezing in the feeling of not being able to fulfill it, will I become special?
もっと手を繋がせて 静寂とトワイライト飛行
Let me hold your hand more, silence and twilight flight.
深く深り 距離まで引き寄せた
Deeply deepening, drawn close to the distance,
月の涙が降ったこの世はまるでstranger
the tears of the moon fell, this world is just like a stranger,
相棒 叫べ
partner, scream!
まさか負荷に落ちていた無重力 ミッドナイト飛行
Unbelievably, the zero gravity fallen into gravity, a midnight flight.
秘密の中で交わって飛ぼう
Let's meet and fly in the secret.
kissで最後まで持って行って マスコットたちの足音が
Keep it up with a kiss until the end, the mascot's footsteps...
交じり合う星に追い果て
chasing to the end of the intersecting stars.
正義が嫌いだなんてこの世はすべて終わった相棒さ
Saying you hate justice, this world is completely finished, partner.
よだれかけのファンタジー オノマトペの雑な渇
A slobbering fantasy, the crude thirst of onomatopoeia,
胸의 膨らみ鼓動 高まる衝動
heartbeat swelling in the chest, a rising urge.
もうどうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
私は勇気が足りないから
Because I lack the courage,
自分を大切にできないんだ
I cannot value myself.
痛みを見ないと気付けやしないんだ
If I don't see the pain, I won't even realize it.
ああ今日も絡めるペイン
Ah, entwined pain again today...
いい子でなきゃ いられないよ だって
Because I can't stay if I'm not a good child,
世界はこんなにも大き彩りで
since the world has such a grand array of colors.
慌忙しく回り 泡立っていたし
Spinning busily, it was foaming,
もっと下手下手 漂うだけの 24/7
just clumsily floating 24/7.
どうすればなんて もう無理 このままではいられない日々
"What should I do?" It's already impossible, in these days where I can't stay like this.
ちょっと怖いけど
It's a little scary, but...
おいてゆく おいてゆく おいてゆく
I'll leave you behind, leave you behind, leave you behind.
これまで手にしてきたブランドもスタイルも
Even the brand and style I've obtained so far,
壊れちゃってもいいや
it's okay even if they break.
だって私は私のためにずっといたいんだもん
Because I want to always exist for myself.
ルートもルールもどうなってもいいよ 13月も
I don't care what happens to routes and rules, even the 13th month,
もっと危ないことしたいんでしょ？
you want to do something even more dangerous, right?
何を犠牲にしたって しょうがないんだよ
It can't be helped, no matter what is sacrificed.
最後までこの胸の痛みだけ抱いて泣いて
Holding only this chest's pain until the end, crying.
ああ今日も絡めるペイン
Ah, entwined pain again today...
曖昧な想いをはぐらかしたって いつかバレちゃうよ
Even if you evade ambiguous feelings, they will eventually be found out.
痛いとか澄むのに 君に言ってるの？どうなの？
Even though it's painful, am I telling you? What about it?
そしたらハニーも
Then, honey too...
...迷っちゃうし
...gets lost,
次の人だって いなくなっちゃうんだ、スウィッチ
...and even the next person will be gone. Switch.
切る
Hang up,
迷っちゃうんだ
or else I'll get lost.
秘密的なことは
There is absolutely
何一つないさ
no secret between us.
もう後悔しないように
So that I won't have any more regrets,
前を向いてできるということ
I'll face forward and do what I can.
置いてゆく 置いてゆく 置いてゆく 置いてゆく
Leaving them behind, leaving them behind...
わがままを手に手にして 泥沼のスタイルも
Taking selfishness into my hands, even in this muddy style...
汚れちゃっても気にしないよ だって私は私に恋していたいんだもの
I don't care if I get dirty, because I want to keep loving myself.
愛してる 愛してる 愛してるよ さよなら
I love you, I love you, I love you, so goodbye.
なんて涙が出ちゃうけど
Saying that makes tears start to fall, but...
何を犠牲にしたって しょうがないんだよ
No matter what I sacrifice, it can't be helped.
今はただこの胸の痛みだけが 頼りだ
Right now, only this pain in my chest is what I rely on.
Yes!
もう私 今日も勇気が足りないから 自分を大切にできないんだ
Because I still lack courage today, I can't take care of myself.
泣くくらいなら少し我慢するんだ
If I'm going to cry, I'd rather endure it a bit.
今日もキャラメルフェイス
Caramel face again today.
冒頭無料配信は終了いたしました。配信チケットは概要欄から！
The free preview has ended. Get your streaming tickets from the description!
The free preview stream has ended. Get your streaming tickets from the description!